A Guide to the Correspondence and Subject Files of the Virginia Secretary of Education, 1975-1997.
Library of Virginia
- Secretary's correspondence and subject files (Accession 32012), 1977-1981., Extent: 21 cubic feet (21 boxes)
  - Virginia Foundation for the Humanities and Public Policy, 1981. (Box 11)
  - Virginia Municipal League, 1981. (Box 11)
  - Virginia Public Building Authority, 1981. (Box 11)
  - Virginia Public School Authority, 1981. (Box 11)
  - Virginia Register Committee, 1981. (Box 11)
  - Virginia School Boards Association, 1981. (Box 11)
  - Virginia School Boards Association - Newsletter, 1981. (Box 11)
  - Virginia Supplemental Retirement System, 1981. (Box 11)
  - Vocational Education, Virginia State Advisory Council on, 1981. (Box 11)
  - Volunteerism, Division of, 1981. (Box 11)
  - W- Miscellaneous, 1981. (Box 11)
  - Yorktown Bicentennial Committee, 1979-1981. (Box 11)
  - Central Garage, 1980-1981. (Box 11)
  - Budget seminar, 1980. (Box 11)
  - Wintergreen seminar, 1981. (Box 11)
  - Office of Education - General, 1981. (Box 11)
  - Office of Education - Budget, 1981. (Box 11)
  - Secretary of Education - General, 1976-1980. (Box 11)
  - Capital Outlay Quarterly Progress Reports, 1980. (Box 11)
  - Virginia Military Institute, 1981. (Box 12)
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University, 1980. (Box 12)
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University, 1982. (Box 12)
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University - Extension Division, 1978. (Box 12)
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University - Extension Division, 1979. (Box 12)
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University - Extension Division, 1980. (Box 12)
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University - Extension Division, 1981. (Box 12)
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University - Extension Division, 1982. (Box 12)
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University - Financial plan, 1982. (Box 12)
  - Dept. of Education budget (1982-1984), 1981. (Box 13)
  - Budget cuts - Federal, 1981. (Box 13)
  - Basic aid funding alternatives (1982-1984), 1981. (Box 13)
  - Office of Education biennial budget (1982-1984), 1981. (Box 13)
  - Budget targets (1982-1984), 1981. (Box 13)
  - Office of Education - Budget (1982-1984) - Working file, 1981. (Box 13)
  - Guidance memoranda (1982-9184 biennial budget), 1981. (Box 13)
  - Education - General Fund transfer forms, 1980-1982. (Box 13)
  - Budget preparation materials (1982-1984), 1981. (Box 13)
  - Budget - Governor's Guidance Package (1982-1984), 1981. (Box 13)
  - Dept. of Planning and Budget, 1978-1981. (Box 13)
  - Dept. of Planning and Budget - Forms, 1981. (Box 13)
  - Dept. of Education - Comparison budget charts, 1980-1982. (Box 13)
  - General budget information charts, 1980. (Box 13)
  - Dept. of Education budget (1980-1982), 1979. (Box 13)
  - Budget amendments, 1981. (Box 13)
  - Addenda budgets - Agencies (1980-1982), 1979. (Box 13)
  - Guidanace memoranda - Agencies (1980-1982) 1979. (Box 13)
  - Budget forms, 1976-1980. (Box 13)
  - Budget Workshop, 1980 May. (Box 13)
  - Financial Exhibit and Program Exhibit for Secretary of Education (1980-1982), 1979. (Box 13)
  - Office of Education - Expenditures, 1980-1981. (Box 13)
  - Subscriptions to publications, 1979-1980. (Box 13)
  - Travel and seminars, 1979-1980. (Box 13)
  - Equipment and supplies, 1979-1980. (Box 13)
  - Invoices, 1980-1982. (Box 13)
  - Monthly expeditures - Secretary's Office, 1978-1979. (Box 13)
  - Monthly expenditures - Secretary's Office, 1979-1980. (Box 13)
  - Miscellaneous budget - Secretary's Office, 1978-1980. (Box 13)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia (SCHEV), 1981. (Box 14)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia (SCHEV) - Meeting, 1980 Dec. (Box 14)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia (SCHEV) - Seminar, 1980 Dec. (Box 14)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia (SCHEV) - Meeting, 1982 Jan. (Box 14)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia (SCHEV) - Meeting, 1981 Dec. (Box 14)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia (SCHEV) - Report on Need for Graduate Instruction and Continued Education in Engineering, 1981. (Box 14)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia (SCHEV) - Developmental Education in Virginia, undated. (Box 14)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia (SCHEV) - Financial Advisory Committee, 1981. (Box 14)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia (SCHEV) - Instructional Programs Advisory Committee, 1981. (Box 14)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia (SCHEV) - Virginia Plan for Higher Education, 1981. (Box 14)
  - Christopher Newport College, 1981. (Box 14)
  - George Mason University, 1981. (Box 14)
  - James Madison University, 1981. (Box 14)
  - Longwood College, 1981. (Box 14)
  - Medical College of Virginia, 1981. (Box 14)
  - Norfolk State University, 1981. (Box 14)
  - Old Dominion University, 1981. (Box 14)
  - Radford, 1981. (Box 14)
  - University of Virginia, 1980-1981. (Box 14)
  - Virginia Military Institute, 1981. (Box 14)
  - Virginia Tech, 1981. (Box 14)
  - Virginia Tech - Veterinary medical education, 1981. (Box 14)
  - Virginia Community College System - Systems Office, 1981. (Box 14)
  - Virginia Community College System - Community colleges, 1981. (Box 14)
  - College of William and Mary, 1981. (Box 14)
  - Correspondence to the Governor's Office, 1981-1982. (Box 14)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1981. (Box 14)
  - Budget (1980-1982), 1981. (Box 14)
  - Women in higher education administration, 1980. (Box 14)
  - Virginia Resource Information System, 1978. (Box 14)
  - Advertising by institutions of higher education, 1979. (Box 14)
  - Capital outlay recommendations, 1979. (Box 14)
  - Center for Excellence, 1979. (Box 14)
  - Compensation Survey for Selected States, 1980. (Box 14)
  - Financial assistance, 1980. (Box 14)
  - Agency personnel plans (1980-1982), 1979-1980. (Box 14)
  - Positions/Enrollments, 1979-1982. (Box 14)
  - Private higher education institutions, 1981. (Box 14)
  - Salaries, 1979. (Box 14)
  - Research material on small rural community colleges, 1978. (Box 14)
  - Title IX, 1979. (Box 14)
  - Budget (1982-1984), 1981. (Box 14)
  - Biennium Budget targets (1980-1982), 1979. (Box 15)
  - Capital Outlay - Manual Section III, 1981. (Box 15)
  - Capital Outlay - Requests for amendments, 1981-1982. (Box 15)
  - Capital Outlay - Special exception requests, 1981. (Box 15)
  - Capital Outlay - Central Appropriations special exception requests, 1981. (Box 15)
  - Capital Outlay - Reversion of General Fund special exception requests, 1981. (Box 15)
  - Capital Outlay - Tour, 1981. (Box 15)
  - Capital Outlay - Biennium (1982-1984), 1981. (Box 15)
  - Capital Outlay - Budget Biennium (1982-1984), 1981. (Box 15)
  - Capital Outlay - Exceptional Action request forms for 1981 Session, 1980. (Box 15)
  - Capital Outlay - Progress Reports, 1981. (Box 15)
  - Dept. of Planning and Budget - Program Proposals (1982-1984), 1981. (Box 16)
  - Dept. of Planning and Budget - Directives, 1981. (Box 16)
  - Dept. of Planning and Budget - General, 1981. (Box 16)
  - Dept. of Planning and Budget - Budget amendments for short session, 1980-1981. (Box 16)
  - Dept. of Planning and Budget - Recommendations on education and general operating budget requests (1982-1984), 1981. (Box 16)
  - Dept. of Planning and Budget - Central Appropriations, 1981. (Box 16)
  - Dept. of Planning and Budget - Budget calendars (1982-1984), 1981. (Box 16)
  - Dept. of Planning and Budget - Agency Guidance Memorandums (1982-1984), 1981. (Box 16)
  - Dept. of Planning and Budget - Requested Amendments (1982-1984), 1982. (Box 16)
  - Dept. of Planning and Budget - Biennium budget targets (1982-1984), 1981. (Box 16)
  - Dept. of Planning and Budget - Issue Identification / Areas of emphasis (1982-1984), 1981. (Box 16)
  - Dept. of Planning and Budget - Budget addenda (1980-1982), 1979. (Box 16)
  - Dept. of Planning and Budget - Revenue bonds (1980-1982), 1979. (Box 16)
  - Dept. of Planning and Budget - Agency Guidance Memoranda (1980-1982), 1979. (Box 16)
  - Commission for the Arts, 1981. (Box 17)
  - Virginia Community College System, 1981. (Box 17)
  - Virginia Community College System - News clippings, 1981. (Box 17)
  - Virginia Community College System - Master Plan for Computing, 1981. (Box 17)
  - Virginia Community College System - Germanna Community College, 1981. (Box 17)
  - Virginia Community College System - Virginia Western Community College, 1981. (Box 17)
  - Virginia Community College System - Virginia Western Community College / WVWR Radio Station, 1981. (Box 17)
  - Virginia Community College System - Western Campus in Goochland, 1981. (Box 17)
  - Dept. of Education, 1981. (Box 17)
  - Dept. of Education, 1982. (Box 17)
  - Dept. of Education - News clippings, 1981. (Box 17)
  - Dept. of Education - News clippings, 1982. (Box 17)
  - Dept. of Education - Travel, 1981. (Box 17)
  - Dept. of Education - Public school financing, 1908-1981. (Box 17)
  - Dept. of Education - Bilingual education, 1981. (Box 17)
  - Dept. of Education - Letters concerning family life education, 1980-1981. (Box 17)
  - Dept. of Education - Teacher salaries, 1980. (Box 17)
  - Dept. of Education - No loss provision, 1979. (Box 17)
  - SCHEV - Presidential salaries, 1981-1982. (Box 17)
  - SCHEV - President compensation, 1979-1981. (Box 17)
  - SCHEV - President compensation - Survey, 1980. (Box 17)
  - Joint Legislative Audit and Review Commission (JLARC) - Meeting, 1979 June. (Box 18)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts, 1981. (Box 18)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts - Dept. of Education, 1981. (Box 18)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts - Virginia Community College System, 1978. (Box 18)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts - State Council on Higher Education for Virginia, 1981. (Box 18)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts - Virginia State Library, 1981. (Box 18)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts - Science Museum of Virginia, 1981. (Box 18)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts - Christopher Newport College, 1981. (Box 18)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts - George Mason University, 1981. (Box 18)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts - James Madison Universtiy, 1981. (Box 18)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts - Longwood College, 1981. (Box 18)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts - Mary Washington College, 1980. (Box 18)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts - Norfolk State University, 1981. (Box 18)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts - Old Dominion Universtiy, 1979. (Box 18)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts - Radford University, 1981. (Box 18)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts - Richard Bland College, 1981. (Box 18)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts - University of Virginia, 1981. (Box 18)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts - Virginia Associated Research Campus, 1981. (Box 18)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts - Virginia Commonwealth University, 1981. (Box 18)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts - Medical College of Virginia (VCU), 1978. (Box 18)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts - Virginia Military Institute, 1980. (Box 18)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts - Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University, 1977-1981. (Box 18)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts - Virginia State University, 1981. (Box 19)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts - Virginia Truck and Ornamental Research, 1977. (Box 19)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts - College of William and Mary, 1978. (Box 19)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts - Virginia Institute of Marine Science, 1981. (Box 19)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts - Virginia School for the Deaf and Blind at Staunton, 1978. (Box 19)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts - Virginia School for the Deaf and Blind at Hampton, 1979. (Box 19)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts - Blue Ridge Community College, 1979. (Box 19)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts - Central Virginia Community College, 1981. (Box 19)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts - Dabney S. Lancaster Community College, 1981. (Box 19)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts - Danville Community College, 1979. (Box 19)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts - Eastern Shore Community College, 1980. (Box 19)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts - Germanna Community College, 1979. (Box 19)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts - J. Sargeant Reynolds Community College, 1978. (Box 19)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts - John Tyler Community College, 1979. (Box 19)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts - Lord Fairfax Community College, 1981. (Box 19)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts - Mountain Empire Community College, 1980. (Box 19)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts -New River Community College, 1980. (Box 19)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts - Northern Virginia Community College, 1980. (Box 19)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts - Patrick Henry Community College, 1980. (Box 19)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts - Paul D. Camp Community College, 1981. (Box 19)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts - Piedmont Virginia Community College, 1978. (Box 19)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts - Rappahannock Community College, 1981. (Box 19)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts - Southside Community College, 1980. (Box 19)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts - Southwest Virginia Community College, 1980. (Box 19)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts - Tidewater Community College, 1981. (Box 19)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts - Virginia Highland Community College, 1980. (Box 19)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts - Virginia Western Community College, 1978. (Box 19)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts - Wytheville Community College, 1980. (Box 19)
  - Responses on local accounts, 1980. (Box 19)
  - Agencies and institutions assigned to the Office of Education, 1981. (Box 19)
  - Christopher Newport College, 1981. (Box 20)
  - Clinch Valley College, 1981. (Box 20)
  - James Madison University, 1982. (Box 20)
  - George Mason University, 1981. (Box 20)
  - James Madison University, 1981. (Box 20)
  - Longwood College, 1980. (Box 20)
  - Longwood College, 1981. (Box 20)
  - Mary Washington College, 1981. (Box 20)
  - James Monroe Memorial Foundation, 1980-1981. (Box 20)
  - Norfolk State University, 1982. (Box 20)
  - Norfolk State University, 1981. (Box 20)
  - Old Dominion University, 1981. (Box 20)
  - Radford University, 1981. (Box 20)
  - Richard Bland College, 1982. (Box 20)
  - Richard Bland College, 1981. (Box 20)
  - University of Virginia, 1982. (Box 20)
  - University of Virginia, 1981. (Box 20)
  - Virginia Commonwealth University, 1982. (Box 20)
  - Virginia Commonwealth University, 1981. (Box 20)
  - Virginia Commonwealth University / Medical College of Virginia, 1981. (Box 20)
  - Virginia Commonwealth University / Virginia Community College System Center, 1977-1978. (Box 20)
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University, 1981. (Box 20)
  - Special Education, 1980. (Box 21)
  - Special Education, 1977-1978. (Box 21)
  - Special Education - Interagency agreements, 1980. (Box 21)
  - Special Education - References, 1980. (Box 21)
  - Special Education - Virginia Developmental Disabilites Protection and Advocacy, 1980. (Box 21)
  - Special Education - Commissioner for the Visually Handicapped, 1980. (Box 21)
  - Special Education - Overall Advisory Council on Needs of Handicapped Children and Adults, 1980. (Box 21)
  - Special Education - Virginia Council for the Deaf, 1980. (Box 21)
  - Special Education - Traineeship loans and teacher preparation programs, 1978. (Box 21)
  - Special Education - Special Education Facility Study (HJR 264), 1980. (Box 21)
  - Special Education - Inservice training, 1979. (Box 21)
  - Special Education - GOW School, 1979. (Box 21)
  - Special Education - Mrs. Larry Lavinder, 1978. (Box 21)
  - Special Education - Mr. and Mrs. Wallace Williams, 1981. (Box 21)
  - Special Education - Prescription Team (HJR 49), 1978. (Box 21)
  - Special Education - Residential facilities, 1981. (Box 21)
  - Special Education - Handicapped Children in State-Operated Facilities, 1980. (Box 21)
  - Special Education - Emotionally Disturbed Children Commission, 1980. (Box 21)
  - Special Education - Emotionally Disturbed Children Commission, 1981. (Box 21)
  - Dept. of Education - Budget, 1981. (Box 21)
- Secretary's correspondence and subject files (Accession 32651), 1975-1985 (bulk 1982-1984)., Extent: 29 cubic feet (29 boxes)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia - ADP Policy, 1982-1984. (Box 1)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia - Advisory Council for Educational Computing, 1983-1984. (Box 1)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia - Advisory Council for Educational Computing, 1983. (Box 1)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia - Annual Conference for Potential Graduates of VSU, 1984. (Box 1)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia - Auxiliary Enterprise, 1984. (Box 1)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia - Auxiliary Enterprise, 1982-1983. (Box 1)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia - Auxiliary Members, 1984. (Box 1)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia - Budget and money matters, 1982-2984. (Box 1)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia - Materials for Special Committee on Higher Education, Budget, 1983. (Box 1)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia - Budget and money matters, 1982. (Box 1)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia - Budgeting and reporting responsibilities, 1984. (Box 1)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia - Capital Outlay, 1983. (Box 1)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia - Classified positions, 1984. (Box 1)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia - Computing Subcommittee, 1984. (Box 1)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia - Consolidated Salary Authorization for Teaching, 1984-1985. (Box 1)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia - Council Members, 1983. (Box 1)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia - Domiciliary Status, 1983. (Box 1)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia - Coordinated Library Services, 1982-1983. (Box 1)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia - Degree Program Productivity, 1984. (Box 1)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia - Economic Development, 1984. (Box 1)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia - Eminent Scholars Program, 1983. (Box 1)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia - Enrollment Projections, 1983-1986. (Box 1)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia - Faculty Salaries, 1984. (Box 2)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia - Faculty Salaries, 1982-1983. (Box 2)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia - Financial Aid, 1982-1984. (Box 2)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia - Finance Advisory Committee, 1984. (Box 2)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia - Finance Advisory Committee, 1982. (Box 2)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia - Foreign student tuition, 1982-1984. (Box 2)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia - Funding Higher Education in the 1990s, 1984. (Box 2)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia - Bills passed by 1985 General Assembly, 1985. (Box 2)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia - General Professional Advisory Committee, 1982-1985. (Box 2)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia - Graduated by Race, 1980. (Box 2)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia - Indirect Costing Procedure, 1983-1984. (Box 2)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia - IPAC, 1982-1984. (Box 2)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia - In-State Tuition, 1984. (Box 2)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia - Liberal Arts Conference, 1984. (Box 2)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia - Library Budgeting Subcommittee, 1984. (Box 2)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia - News articles, 1984. (Box 2)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia - Paper on Higher Education Issues, 1982. (Box 2)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia - Off-Campus Instruction Report, 1982. (Box 2)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia - OCR, 1983. (Box 2)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia - Physical Plant Guidelines Subcommittee, 1984. (Box 2)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia - JTCs Requests to the Council, undated. (Box 2)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia - Service Learning Conference, 1985. (Box 2)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia - Space Planning Guidelines, 1984. (Box 2)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia - Statewide Library Services, 1984. (Box 2)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia - Tuition Assistance Grant, 1982-1984. (Box 2)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia - Tuition Fee and Task Force, 1982-1984. (Box 2)
  - Virginia Community College System - General, 1982-1984. (Box 3)
  - Virginia Community College System - Virginia Community Colleges Association, 1983-1984. (Box 3)
  - Virginia Community College System - Annual meeting, 1984. (Box 3)
  - Virginia Community College System - Audit Report, 1982-1984. (Box 3)
  - Virginia Community College System - Budget, money matters and audit, 1981-1983. (Box 3)
  - Virginia Community College System - Building Community College partnerships with the private sector, 1982-1983. (Box 3)
  - Virginia Community College System - Central Office Supply, 1982-1983. (Box 3)
  - Virginia Community College System - Enrollment Projection and Review, 1982-1984. (Box 3)
  - Virginia Community College System - Equipment, 1984. (Box 3)
  - Virginia Community College System - Grievance procedure, 1982. (Box 3)
  - Virginia Community College System - Industrial Training Division, 1982-1984. (Box 3)
  - Virginia Community College System - Job Training, Kellogg Foundation Work Project, 1983. (Box 3)
  - Virginia Community College System - Legislative Plan, 1983-1984. (Box 3)
  - Virginia Community College System - Personnel, 1981-1984. (Box 3)
  - Virginia Community College System - Policy Manual, 1985. (Box 3)
  - Virginia Community College System - President salaries, 1984. (Box 3)
  - Virginia Community College System - Presidential Selection/Compensation, 1982. (Box 3)
  - Virginia Community College System - General Condition of Public Facilities Report, 1983. (Box 3)
  - Virginia Community College System - Restricted amounts, 1984. (Box 3)
  - Virginia Community College System - Self Study, 1983. (Box 3)
  - Virginia Community College System - Targets, 1983. (Box 3)
  - Virginia Community College System - Blue Ridge CC, 1982-1984. (Box 3)
  - Virginia Community College System - Central Virginia CC, 1982-1984. (Box 3)
  - Virginia Community College System - Dabney S. Lancaster CC, 1982-1983. (Box 3)
  - Virginia Community College System - Danville CC, 1982-1984. (Box 3)
  - Virginia Community College System - Eastern Shore CC, 1983. (Box 3)
  - Virginia Community College System - Germanna CC, 1982-1984. (Box 3)
  - Virginia Community College System - John Tyler CC, 1982-1984. (Box 3)
  - Virginia Community College System - J. Sargeant Reynolds CC, 1982-1984. (Box 3)
  - Virginia Community College System - Lord Fairfax CC, 1983. (Box 3)
  - Virginia Community College System - Mountain Empire CC, 1983-1984. (Box 3)
  - Virginia Community College System - New River CC, 1982-1984. (Box 3)
  - Virginia Community College System - Northern Virginia CC, 1982-1984. (Box 3)
  - Virginia Community College System - Northern Virginia CC - Budget, money matters, audit, 1982-1983. (Box 3)
  - Virginia Community College System - Northern Virginia CC - Brault Building and Dedication, 1984. (Box 3)
  - Virginia Community College System - Patrick Henry CC, 1982-1984. (Box 3)
  - Virginia Community College System - Paul D. Camp CC, 1982-1983. (Box 3)